MEN:
I can't believe this,
but I managed to book a ticket to Singapore.
I will be on the seven o'clock flight tomorrow morning.
WOMAN:
That's great.
Does that mean that you will get to see your friend who moved out
there a few years back after you are finished meeting with Mr. Wang?
MEN:
I am not sure because Mr.
Wang will probably want to take me around the plant site on the day I arrive there.
I am hoping that I will be able to see my friend the day
after,
but he mentioned that he might have to leave town that day.
He said he would try to rearrange his trip,
but I have not spoken to him for a few days.
I will call him tonight to see if he is able to do that.
WOMAN:
You should just take your vacation early and spend a week there after you
take care of your business.
It's not like you get to travel to the Far East all the time, you know.